{
    "subject": "resource/Clark_Haggans",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/isPrimaryTopicOf",
    "object": "http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Clark_Haggans",
    "human_readable": "Clark Haggans is primarily about Clark Haggans.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9657394289970398,
            "question": "What is Clark Haggans primarily known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9074820280075073,
            "question": "Who is Clark Haggans?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7546160221099854,
            "question": "What is Clark Haggans most famous for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7414321899414062,
            "question": "Was Clark Haggans a successful athlete?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7403549551963806,
            "question": "What position did Clark Haggans play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7071494460105896,
            "question": "Can you tell me something about Clark Haggans's career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7034235596656799,
            "question": "Which sports league was Clark Haggans a part of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6968899369239807,
            "question": "What team did Clark Haggans play for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6784032583236694,
            "question": "What is Clark Haggans's primary area of expertise?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.653252124786377,
            "question": "In what profession did Clark Haggans excel?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Clark Haggans is primarily about Clark Haggans.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1498_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Clark Haggans's primary area of expertise?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1498_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What team did Clark Haggans play for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1498_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which sports league was Clark Haggans a part of?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1498_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1498_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1498_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1498_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1498_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1498_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1498_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1498_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1498_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1498_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1498_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here's my evaluation of whether the information supports the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nThe reason for this answer is that none of the documents suggest that Clark Haggans' primary topic or subject is himself. The majority of the texts focus on his achievements and activities as a football player, particularly with the Pittsburgh Steelers. While some documents do mention Clark Haggans, they are generally discussing his career, games, or charitable work, rather than his personal life or self.\n\nTherefore, based on the provided context information, it appears that Clark Haggans is not primarily about himself, but rather about his football career and accomplishments."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe provided documents contain extensive information about Clark Haggans, his career in the NFL, achievements, and personal life. Therefore, it can be concluded that the information is indeed primarily about Clark Haggans."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The context information is predominantly about Clark Haggans' life, career, and achievements as an NFL player, and not primarily about him. The details provided are largely focused on his playing history, Super Bowl wins, charitable work, and personal life, which collectively paint a comprehensive picture of who he was as a person.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}